Guide to the Ithaca House Archive, 1969 - 1986
Ithaca House Archive, 1969 - 1986
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ithaca House archive,1969 - 1986
4679
Ithaca House
11 cubic feet
Manuscripts, correspondence, photographs, mock-ups, 2 audiocassettes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Manuscripts and material relating to books published by Ithaca House press; Business records of Ithaca House Press and Ithaca House Gallery and Bookstore.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Ithaca House was a small poetry press founded by Baxter Hathaway, Professor of English at Cornell University, in December 1969. It published more than 100 titles during its 15 year existence which were produced by letter press and distributed through Serendipity (the forerunner of what is today Small Press Distribution) in Berkeley, CA. Ithaca House poets include Ron Silliman, Ray DiPalma, Bob Perelman, Maxine Chernoff, Tom Mandel, Stephen Shrader, Steve Katz, Rochelle Nameroff, and David Gitin. Also included are the works of Native American poets Joe Bruchac, Ralph Salisbury, and Peter Wild; as well as the work of African-American poets C. S. Giscombe, William J Harris, and Kenneth McClane.
Ithaca House Gallery and Bookstore opened in 1970 and sold books published by Ithaca House Press as well as crafts made by local artisans.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes manuscripts and typescripts; publisher's comment notes; book reviews; mock-ups; cover artwork and photos; Library of Congress cards; and other material relating to books published by Ithaca House Press. The collection also includes correspondence, business records, grant applications, small press newsletters, and other files related to the operation of the press.
Material relating to the Ithaca House Gallery and Bookstore includes newspaper articles, announcements, catalogs, and photographs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Silliman, Ronald, 1946-; Perelman, Bob; Chernoff, Maxine, 1952-; Mandel, Tom, 1942-; Shrader, Stephen.; Katz, Steve, 1935-; Nameroff, Rochelle, 1943-; Gitin, David; Bruchac, Joseph, 1942-; Salisbury, Ralph J; Giscombe, C. S., 1950-; Harris, William J., 1942-; DiPalma, Ray.; Wild, Peter, 1940-; McClane, Kenneth A., 1951
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
Baxter Hathaway. Papers, #14-12-2198. Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Series I: Author Files contains manuscripts, correspondence, mock-ups, and other materials relating to authors published by Ithaca House Press as well as correspondence to and from authors of manuscripts rejected by Ithaca House Press.
Series II: Business Files is made up of material relating to the business operations of Ithaca House Press and Ithaca House Gallery and Bookstore.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Author Files
Boxes 1-8
Series II. Business Files
Boxes 8-11
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Author Files
  - Published Author Files
    - Allardt, Linda,1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      The Names of the Survivors, 2 typescript versions
  - Allardt, Linda,1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    correspondence, reviews, announcement & review copy lists, Library of Congress card
  - Allen, Robert,1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Valhalla at the OK, typescript & final layout
  - Allen, Robert,1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Blues & Ballads, typescript, lists of corrections, bio. note, misc. notes
  - Allen, Robert,1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    correspondence, back cover photograph, misc. notes & promotional materials
  - Anderson, Mark,1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    The Broken Boat, typescript, notes about physical specifications
  - Anderson, Mark,1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, announcement cards, cover art, Library of Congress card
  - Bertolino, James,1970-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, reviews, curriculum vitae, review copy list
  - Bradley, Ardyth,1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Inside the Bones is Flesh, 3 typescript versions
  - Bradley, Ardyth,1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, review copy list, announcement card, internal notes on manuscript, Library of Congress card, reviews, errata cards
  - Bruchac, Joseph,1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Indian Mountain and other poems, typescript
  - Bruchac, Joseph,1970-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, internal notes on manuscript, republication permissions, bio. note, reviews, catalogue, printed book covers
  - Buckley, Christopher,1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Last Rites, 2 typescript versions and internal notes on manuscript
  - Buckley, Christopher,1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Other Lives, 3 typescript versions & a final layout version
  - Buckley, Christopher,1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, reviews, advertisements, announcement cards, review copy lists, printed book covers, printing notes, internal notes on manuscript, original cover art, republication permissions, Library of Congress card, errata card, curriculum vitae [continued in following folder]
  - Buckley, Christopher,1979-1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    [continued from previous folder, see above for description]
  - Buell, Frederick,1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Theseus and other poems, typescript and galley proof
  - Buell, Frederick,1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Objective Mysteries, typescript [later published by Wesleyan U.P under title Full Summer, (1979)]
  - Buell, Frederick,1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, review copy lists, announcement cards, reviews, bio. note, orign. cover photographs, sales notes, catalogue
  - Bullis, Jerald,1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Taking Up the Serpent, 4 typescript versions
  - Bullis, Jerald,1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Adorning the Buckhorn Helmet, 2 typescripts & final layout
  - Bullis, Jerald,1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, announcement cards, reviews, review lists, bio. note, author photograph, printed covers (both books), incomplete poem typescripts
  - Burke, Carol,1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, reviews
  - Burrows, Edwin Gladding,1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Kiva, typescript
  - Burrows, Edwin Gladding,1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    The House of August, typescript & final layout version
  - Burrows, Edwin Gladding,1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, reviews, ad proofs, announcement cards, original cover art, internal manuscript notes, review lists, republication permissions, typescript of pulled poems & early versions from The House of August
  - Chernoff, Maxine,1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    New Faces of 1952, 2 typescript versions & final layout version
  - Chernoff, Maxine,1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, announcement cards, reviews, internal manuscript notes, republication permissions, original cover art
  - Coffin, Lyn,1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    The Poetry of Wickedness, typescript
  - Coffin, Lyn,1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, reviews, internal manuscript notes, cover art, Library of Congress card, announcement cards
  - D'Abate, Richard,1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, announcement list, final title pages & covers, announcement card, internal formatting notes, bio. note
  - DiPalma, Raymond,1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    The Gallery Goers, typescript
  - DiPalma, Raymond,1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Soli, typescript, final layout version & internal manuscript notes
  - DiPalma, Raymond,1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, reviews, catalogue, author photograph, bio. note, contents & acknowledgements pages, announcements
  - Driscoll, Jack,1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Fishing the Backwash, 2 typescript versions & a final layout version
  - Driscoll, Jack,1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    [folder 1 of 2] Correspondence, review cards, reviews, adverisement proof, review lists, internal notes on printing, announcement cards, republication permissions, cover art
  - Driscoll, Jack,1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    [folder 2 of 2] Correspondence, &c.
  - Epstein, Judy,1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Review
  - Everman, Welch D.,1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Orion, typescript
  - Everman, Welch D.,1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, review copy list, announcement list, bio. note, announcement card, re-writes of manuscript
  - Fifer, Ken,1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Falling Man, 2 typescript versions
  - Fifer, Ken,1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, reviews, announcement cards, republication permissions, review & announcement lists, Library of Congress card, original cover art, author photograph, internal manuscript notes, bio. note
  - Flaherty, Doug,1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Love-Tangle of Roots, 2 typescripts & final layout version
  - Flaherty, Doug,1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, original cover art & author photographs, rejected manuscript revisions, republication permissions, acquisition list, announcement list, review list, announcement cards, printed cover, internal manuscript notes, reviews, Library of Congress card, essay on poetics
  - Flaherty, Doug,1975-1977 (Box 11)
    Metal type stamps for Love-Tangle of Roots,
  - Flanagan, Robert,1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, original printed cover
  - Fogel, Daniel Mark,1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, original printed cover, reviews, announcement card
  - Fortunato, Peter,1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Correspondence from & about author, reviews
  - Friedman, B.H.,1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Whispers, typescript
  - Friedman, B.H.,1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Whispers, later typescript
  - Friedman, B.H.,1971-1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, reviews, announcement cards, printed covers (softbound & hardbound editions), internal manuscript notes, catalogue, reprinting notes, author photograph
  - Frost, Carol,1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    The Liar's Dice, 2 typescript versions
  - Frost, Carol,1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    The Fearful Child, 3 typescript versions & final layout version
  - Frost, Carol,1977-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, advertisement proof, review & announcment copy lists, republication permissions, internal printing notes, internal manuscript notes, errata slips, printed covers ( Liar's Dice), Library of Congress card, announcement cards ( Liar's Dice), cover art (a few items slightly discoloured due to water damage)
  - Gillespie, Robert,1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    The Man Chain, 2 typescript versions
  - Gillespie, Robert,1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Correspondence from & to author, reviews, announcement cards, republication permissions, internal manuscript notes, Library of Congress card (a few items slightly discoloured due to water damage
  - Gilliland, Mary,1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Gathering Fire, typescript & final layout version
  - Gilliland, Mary,1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, reading announcements, review lists, reviews, cover mock-up, internal notes on printing, laudatory blurbs, announcement flyers, Library of Congress card
  - Giscombe, Cecil S.,1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Postcards, typescript
  - Giscombe, Cecil S.,1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, printed cover, Library of Congress card, reviews, internal manuscript notes
  - Gitin, David,1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    City Air, typescript & final layout version
  - Gitin, David,1972-1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, review & announcement lists, internal manuscript notes, announcement card, republication permissions, cover blurb, author photograph, review, mock-up
  - Gitin, Maria,1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Little Movies, typescript
  - Gitin, Maria,1973-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, author photograph, announcement cards, review, internal manuscript notes, review & announcement lists, cover blurb, bio. note
  - Goedicke, Patricia,1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    For the Four Corners, typescript & final layout version
  - Goedicke, Patricia,1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    The Trail that Turns on Itself, 3 typescript versions
  - Goedicke, Patricia,1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, cover blurb, reviews, advertisement, republication permissions, internal manuscript notes, bio. note, curriculum vitae, review lists, announcement cards, announcement lists, original cover design, test printings of cover text, final covers, Library of Congress card
  - Goldbarth, Albert,1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Keeping, typescript
  - Goldbarth, Albert,1972-1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, reviews, final cover, internal manuscript notes
  - Greenberg, Alvin,1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    The Dark Lands, typescript
  - Greenberg, Alvin,1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, review list, reviews, internal manuscript notes, final cover, announcements, original cover art
  - Hanson, Karen,1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Spine, typescript & final layout version
  - Hanson, Karen,1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    book mock-ups, reviews, republication permissions, internal printing notes, final title pages, cover photograph, announcements, catalogue
  - Harris, William J.,1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Hey Fella Would You Mind Holding this Piano a Moment, typescript
  - Harris, William J.,1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    In My Own Dark Way, typescript
  - Harris, William J.,1974-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, reprint request, review copy list, reviews, internal manuscript notes, printed covers, Library of Congress card
  - Hathaway, Baxter,1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    "The Petulant Children" typescript
  - Hathaway, Baxter,1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, reviews & misc. clippings in re author, typescript of unpublished memoir (incomplete), final C. Review essay, Library of Congress card, final cover, announcement cards
  - Hathaway, James,1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Foraging & Other Poems, typescript
  - Hathaway, James,1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Reviews, republication permission, orig. cover art
  - Hathaway, William,1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    True Confessions & False Romances, typescript & final layout version
  - Hathaway, William,1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    A Wilderness of Monkeys, typescript
  - Hathaway, William,1970-1985 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, reviews, original cover, catalogue, press release, announcement, Library of Congress card
  - Hewitt, Geof,1972-1983 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, acknowledgements, republication permissions, reviews, announcement list, review copy lists
  - Kallet, Marilyn,1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Devils Live So Near, 1 complete & 1 partial typescript version
  - Kallet, Marilyn,1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    In the Great Night, 2 typescript versions
  - Kallet, Marilyn,1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, acknowledgements, internal manuscript notes, announcement lists, review lists, printed cover, announcement card, Library of Congress card, review, errata slips
  - Katz, Steve,1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Cheyenne River Wild Track, typescript & final layout version
  - Katz, Steve,1972-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, reviews, book mock-up, internal manuscript notes, original cover art
  - Kelly, David M.,1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Filming Assassinations, 2 typescript versions
  - Kelly, David M.,1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, reviews, announcements, review list, announcement list, internal manuscript notes, republication permissions, library of congress card
  - Knauth, Stephen,1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Night-Fishing on Irish Buffalo Creek, 2 typescript versions
  - Knauth, Stephen,1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Correspondence from & to author, reviews, republication permissions, original cover art, printed cover & cover layout, review list, announcement list
  - Kuzma, Greg,1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Song for Someone Going Away, typescript & final layout version
  - Kuzma, Greg,1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Correspondence from & to author, republication permissions, reviews, internal manuscript notes
  - Latta, John,1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Rubbing Torsos, typescript
  - Latta, John,1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, internal manuscript notes, review copy list, announcement list, announcements, Library of Congress card, draft of article about B. Hathaway
  - Mandel, Tom,1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Ready to Go, typescript
  - Mandel, Tom,1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Correspondence from, to & about author, reviews
  - Marz, Roy,1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    The Island-Maker, typescript & final layout version
  - Marz, Roy,1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    [folder 1 of 2] Correspondence about author [includes corr. from B. Hathaway to Blaine Marz dated 5/22/82 detailing full history of Ithaca House], advertisements, printed covers, original cover art, drafts of book forward, Imperial Hill typescript, reviews, republication permissions, announcement & review copy lists, announcements
  - Marz, Roy,1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - McAleavey, David,1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    The Forty Days, typescript
  - McAleavey, David,1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Shrine, Shelter, Cave, (a/k/a Secrets Souvenirs, ), 2 typescript versions
  - McAleavey, David,1971-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, jacket blurbs, bio. note, republication permissions, announcements, printed signatures, reviews, photocopy of cover art, printed covers, internal manuscript notes, catalogue
  - McCann, Richard,1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    A Dream of the Traveler, 2 typescript versions
  - McCann, Richard,1973-1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, review list, announcement list, curriculum vitae, republication permissions, internal manuscript notes, Library of Congress card, cover layout
  - McClane, Kenneth,1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Out Beyond the Bay, typescript & final layout version (incomplete)
  - McClane, Kenneth,1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Moons & Low Times, typescript
  - McClane, Kenneth,1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, original cover art, republication permissions, reviews, announcement list, internal manuscript notes, printed covers, Library of Congress card, announcement card
  - McRoberts, Robert,1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Lip Service, typescript
  - McRoberts, Robert,1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, republication permissions, announcement list, review copy list, receipts, internal manuscript notes, Library of Congress card
  - Melnick, David,1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Eclogs, typescript [badly mildewed & wrapped in plastic]
  - Melnick, David,1971-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, original cover photograph, catalogue, printed covers, jacket blurb
  - Moore, John,1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    By Selkirk's Lake and Other Poems, bound typescript
  - Moore, John,1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, curriculum vitae, bio. note, author photographs, catalogue
  - Nameroff, Rochelle,1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Body Prints, typescript
  - Nameroff, Rochelle,1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, original proposed cover art, printed cover, poems removed from collection, catalogue
  - Nathan, Leonard,1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    The Teachings of Grandfather Fox, typescript
  - Nathan, Leonard,1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, review list, announcement list, Library of Congress card, internal manuscript notes, curriculum vitae, announcements, reviews, fully printed book mock-up
  - Orfalea, Gregory,1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Book jacket for The Capital of Solitude, (Greenfield Review Press)
  - Owen, Sue,1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Nursery Rhymes for the Dead, typescript
  - Owen, Sue,1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, reviews, announcement cards, resume, internal manuscript notes
  - Parlatore, Anselm,1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Hybrid Inoculum, 2 typescript versions (earlier titled Crossing)
  - Parlatore, Anselm,1972-1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, announcement cards, announcement list, IH advertisement copy, review copy list, bio. note, reviews
  - Patrick, William B.,1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Letter to the Ghosts, typescript
  - Patrick, William B.,1976-1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, announcement list, printed cover, reviews, announcement card, Library of Congress card, republication permissions, cover blurb
  - Patton, Rob,1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Dare, typescript
  - Patton, Rob,1970-1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, internal manuscript notes, announcements, republication permissions, printed covers, printing notes, catalogue, Library of Congress card
  - Peterfreund, Stuart,1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    The Hanged Knife, typescript
  - Peterfreund, Stuart,1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Harder Than Rain, typescript
  - Peterfreund, Stuart,1969-1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, reviews, printing notes, announcement cards, author photographs, author bio. note, announcement & review lists, printed covers, internal manuscript notes, catalogue, Library of Congress card
  - Peterson, Carl,1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    The Triple Fool, typescript
  - Peterson, Carl,1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    For Anna Akhmatova & Other Poems, typescript & final layout version
  - Peterson, Carl,1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, review list, printed cover, internal manuscript notes, reviews, Library of Congress card
  - Perelman, Bob,1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Braille, two typescript versions
  - Perelman, Bob,1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Piasecki, Bruce,1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Stray Prayers, four typescript versions [folder 1 of 2]
  - Piasecki, Bruce,1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Stray Prayers, [folder 2 of 2]
  - Piasecki, Bruce,1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Correspondence, back cover blurbs, reviews, printed cover, announcement cards, Library of Congress card
  - Rendleman, Danny L.,1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Signals to the Blind, typescript
  - Rendleman, Danny L.,1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    The Winter Rooms, (a/k/a Sailor, ) typescript
  - Rendleman, Danny L.,1970-1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, preliminary cover layout, reviews, catalogue, author bio. note, internal manuscript notes, printing notes, republication permissions, review lists, announcement lists, announcements, curriculum vitae, printed cover
  - Reynolds, Tim,1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Dawn Chorus, typescript
  - Reynolds, Tim,1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    typescripts of two apparently unpublished mss.: Nod, and The Singularity,
  - Reynolds, Tim,1979-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, reviews, Library of Congress card, curriculum vitae, internal manuscript notes, announcement cards, photocopies of cover art [?], draft grant proposal
  - Rindfleisch, Norval,1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    In Loveless Clarity, typescript (has suffered some water damage)
  - Rindfleisch, Norval,1970-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, original cover art, internal manuscript notes, republication permissions, review/announcement list, galleys, jacket blurbs, reviews, announcements, catalogue
  - Saleh, Dennis,1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Palmway, typescript (incomplete)
  - Saleh, Dennis,1974-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, original cover art, reviews, Library of Congress card, internal manuscript notes, printed cover, announcement & review lists
  - Salisbury, Ralph J.,1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Ghost Grapefruit & Other Poems, typescript & final layout version